<resources>
    <string name="martini1">Chill martini glass with soda water and ice. Fill mixing glass to top with ice. Add the dry vermouth to the mixing glass, giving a small stir to coat the ice with the vermouth. Drain out glass, leaving just the coating on the ice. Add the gin to the mixing glass. Stir for 15 seconds, always making sure that the glass is full to the brim with ice. Taste. Fine strain into chilled martini glass. Zest with lemon peel and add twist unto drink.</string>
    <string name="manhattan2">Chill cocktail glass with ice and soda. Fill a mixing glass with ice and then add all ingredients. Using a bar spoon, stir the drink for approximately 20 seconds. When stirring, always ensure the glass is topped up with ice.Taste and then strain into the chilled cocktail glass, serving straight up. Zest the drink and glass with the orange peel and then twist and place in glass.</string>
    <string name="godfather3">Build the ingredients in an Old-Fashioned glass with ice cubes. Stir well and serve.</string>
    <string name="bellini4">Add 4 dashes of peach bitters into chilled champagne flute. Add peach puree and top up with Prosecco.</string>
    <string name="woowoo5">Pour all ingredients into a highball glass over ice cubes, stir with bar spoon for 15 seconds and serve.</string>
    <string name="appletini6">Mix in a shaker and then pour into a chilled cocktail glass. Garnish with apple slice and serve.</string>
    <string name="cantarito7">Rim a Collins glass with salt. Fill the glass with ice and add the tequila and juices.Top it off with grapefruit soda. Garnish with fruit wedges.</string>
    <string name="caipivodka8">Place lime and sugar into Old-Fashioned glass and muddle (mash the two ingredients together using a muddler or a wooden spoon). Fill the glass with crushed ice and add the vodka.</string>
    <string name="beachcomber9">Pour the ingredients into a cocktail shaker with ice cubes. Shake well for 20 seconds. Strain into a chilled cocktail glass.</string>
</resources>