
<resources>
    <string name="merlot1">Merlot is an easy going red known for being both a great wine to create blends with, as well as producing some extraordinary wines of its own. Typically Merlot produces a well-rounded, medium-bodied wine with low acidity and relatively high alcohol levels. Cooler climate varieties have slightly higher tannins, whereas those from warmer climates are full of fruitiness and have lower tannins.</string>
    <string name="malbec2">When we think of Malbec, we tend to think of big, juicy wines perfect for big, juicy steaks! With high tannins, high alcohol and a full body, these deep, rich reds have a wonderful depth of flavour, and are great for ageing.</string>
    <string name="shiraz3"> Shiraz is another popular black grape variety grown across the world. In Old World countries the grape is known as Syrah, and in New World it’s Shiraz. Generally Shiraz is known for its full body, high tannins and medium acidity. It has a deep purple hue, due to its thick, deep coloured skins. Not only is the name different but the style can vary between Old World and New World, despite being the same grape.</string>
    <string name="grenache4">A real unsung hero of the wine world, used in both stunning blends and stand-alone varieties. Typically, Grenache is medium-bodied, high in alcohol and light in colour.</string>
    <string name="tempranillo5">This old, thick-skinned grape is the fourth most widely planted variety in the world, and the most grown red grape in Spain (where it originates). Tempranillo produces medium to full-bodied reds which are ruby in colour when young, turning more garnet with age. High tannins are complemented by reasonable levels of acidity, and high alcohol levels. This variety is commonly used as the base of the world famous Rioja blends.</string>
    <string name="zinfandel6">This rich and reasonably powerful red, now most commonly found across the pond, is a grape full of history. Full-bodied, with a high alcohol content, medium tannins and a kick of acidity, Zinfandel can produce some sensational wines.</string>
    <string name="sangiovese7">A variety known for being notoriously difficult to grow and work with, Sangiovese has gained a bad reputation over the past, however that is beginning to change. Depending on where it is grown, the wine style can vary – although, commonly it produces medium-bodied wines with high tannins and very high acidity. Most are better consumed young, however some are best aged for around four to seven years.</string>
    <string name="carmenere8">Carménère is a less common variety, but certainly worth being on any wine buff’s radar as it produces some outstanding vino – and is thought to be a predecessor to some of the better known red grapes out there, such as Cabernet Franc and Merlot. Known for being a difficult grape to grow, it produces medium-bodied, fruity wines with high acidity, noticeable tannins and a smooth mouthfeel – although the style can vary slightly depending on the region.</string>
</resources>

